So, to get the average deal size for all the accounts,
要计算所有客户的平均交易规模
I've set up a spreadsheet so that we can first calculate
我建了这份表格 首先以美元为单位
the total bookings in dollars that we already did in the past,
如何计算订单总额 已经在上一个视频已经演示了
in the previous video and then the number of deals for each of the accounts,
接着要计算每个客户的交易数量
and then we're going to go ahead and calculate the average deal size.
然后就可以计算出平均交易规模
So first, we're going to go ahead and
首先要做的是
calculate the sum of the bookings for each of these accounts.
计算每个客户的订单金额总量
I'll just copy and paste it down,
复制求和公式到这些单元格
and then the short number of deals where each of the accounts and then again,
然后求和计算每个客户的交易总数
I'm going to just copy this formula down.
再复制公式到这些单元格
I'm going to go ahead and copy these.
接着把得出的数值复制一下
So, I'm going to just go ahead and copy and paste the values,
把相应的值复制粘贴一下
copy and paste the values,
把值复制粘贴之后
and then to get the average deal size that we got from each of
要计算每个客户的平均交易规模
the accounts all you have to do is you divide the total bookings by the number of deals,
只需把订单总额除以交易数量
and that tells you the average amount for
得出我们从每个客户获得的
each deal or that we got from each of these accounts.
平均交易额
Right away, we can see,
可以看到
Sam's Club had really high bookings that it seems to me there was a mix of
Sam's Club 的订单金额很高
monthly and annual subscriptions that we got and the reason is because we know that
看起来像是结合了按月和按年订购
the monthly subscription is $16 and you're yearly subscriptions are $195.
在表格底部 我们看到 按月订购是 16 美元 而按年订购是 195 美元
So, with that knowledge in mind,
了解这个标准之后
we can see that this- the amount that we got from Sam's Club and
我们可以推断出 Sam's Club 和 Costco
Costco was a combination of monthly and yearly accounts, purely orders.
都结合了按月和按年订购 就是这两行的订单情况
So, the average deal size tells us that.
得出的平均交易规模告诉我们
We got a combination of monthly and yearly subscription from Costco and Sam's Club.
Costco 和 Sam's Club 结合了按月和按年订购
Case of Sprouts, the book yield was smaller,
Sprouts 的订单数量比较少
but the booking size was bigger,
但是订单规模比较大
and that's because the average deal size
因为平均交易规模
was a 195 which turns out to be a yearly subscription.
达到 195 美元 是按年订购
So, all of the a 150 deals that we got for Sprouts, for this account,
Sprouts 的 150 笔交易全都是按年订购
were all annual versus in Safeway
而 Safeway 呢
where even though we've gotten the more number of deals,
尽管订单数量比较多
the unit price was $16 which happens to be a monthly subscription.
但是单价是 16 美元 是按月订购
So, we didn't get as much bookings for that.
订单总额没有那么多
But this kind of analysis allows the sales team to see okay,
这样分析之后 销售团队可以了解到
which account is actually generating more bookings for them and focus their efforts
哪些客户带来的订单金额更大
on the type of deals that they get and the type of customer that they're getting.
就可以将更多精力集中在这些交易类型和客户类型上